Okay, so
حسنا فإذاً
90 percent of my photographic process
٩٠ في المئة من عملية التصوير الفوتوغرافي لدي
is, in fact, not photographic.
هي في الواقع ، ليست فوتوغرافية
It involves a campaign of letter writing,
أنها تحتوي على حملة كتابة رسائل،
research and phone calls
بحوث ومكالمات هاتفية
to access my subjects,
للوصول إلى موضوعاتي
which can range from Hamas leaders in Gaza
التي يمكن أن تتراوح من قادة حماس في غزة
to a hibernating black bear in its cave
إلى دب السبات السوداء في كهفه
in West Virginia.
في غرب فيرجينيا .
And oddly, the most notable
والغريب ، النوع أكثر ابرزاً
letter of rejection I ever received
هي رسالة رفض التي تلقيتها
came from Walt Disney World,
من عالم والت ديزني ،
a seemingly innocuous site.
الذي يبدو كموقع حميد.
And it read -- I'm just going to read a key sentence:
يقال فيها، سوف اقرأ الجملة الأساسية
"Especially during these violent times,
"خصوصا في هذه الأوقات العنيفة ،
I personally believe
أنا شخصيا أؤمن
that the magical spell cast upon guests who visit our theme parks
أن السحر المعروض على ضيوفنا الزوار لمتنزهاتنا
is particularly important to protect
له أهمية ليحمى
and helps to provide them with an important fantasy
ويساعد على التوفير خيال هام لهم
they can escape to."
ليمكنهم من الهروب إليه
Photography threatens fantasy.
التصوير يهدد الخيال.
They didn't want to let my camera in
انهم لم يسمحوا لي بإدخال الكاميرا
because it confronts constructed realities, myths and beliefs,
لأنها تواجه الحقائق المشيدة والخرافات والمعتقدات ،
and provides what appears to be
وينص على ما يبدو
evidence of a truth.
أدلة عن الحقيقة.
But there are multiple truths attached to every image,
ولكن هناك حقائق متعددة معلقة على كل صورة،
depending on the creator's intention, the viewer
اعتمادا على نية مبتكر ، المشاهد
and the context in which it is presented.
والسياق الذي يقدمه.
Over a five year period following September 11th,
طوال فترة الخامس سنوات، بعد 11سبتمبر
when the American media and government were seeking
عندما كانت وسائل الاعلام الاميركية والحكومة تبحثان
hidden and unknown sites
عن مواقع مخفية و غير معروفة
beyond its borders,
وراء حدودها ،
most notably weapons of mass destruction,
وبالأخص أسلحة الدمار الشامل ،
I chose to look inward at that which was integral
لقد اخترت أن أنظر إلى الداخل في جزء الكامل
to America's foundation,
من مؤسسات الأميركية ،
mythology and daily functioning.
الأساطير والأداء اليومي.
I wanted to confront the boundaries of the citizen,
كنت أرغب في مواجهة حدود ألمواطن ،
self-imposed and real,
المفروضة ذاتيا‏ و الحقيقية
and confront the divide between privileged
و مواجهة الفجوة بين أصحاب الإمتيازات
and public access to knowledge.
وحق الجمهور في الوصول إلى المعرفة.
It was a critical moment in American history
كانت لحظة حاسمة في التاريخ الأميركي
and global history
والتاريخ العالمي
where one felt they didn't have access to accurate information.
حيث كانو يشعروا بأنهم لم يتمكنوا من الحصول على معلومات دقيقة.
And I wanted to see the center with my own eyes,
وأردت أن أرى المركز بعيناي ،
but what I came away with is a photograph.
ولكن ما خرجت به هو صورة فوتوغرافية.
And it's just another place from which to observe,
وانه مجرد مكان آخر للمراقبة منه ،
and the understanding that
و التفهم أنه
there are no absolute, all-knowing insiders.
لا يوجد مطلقاً ، مطلعين في الداخل يعرفون كل شئ.
And the outsider can never really reach the core.
لا يمكن للدخلاء أبدا الوصول إلى جوهر الأمر.
I'm going to run through some of the photographs in this series.
سوف أقوم بمراجعة سريعة عن بعض الصور في هذه السلسلة.
It's titled, "An American Index
انها بعنوان ، الفهرس الأميركي
of the Hidden and Unfamiliar,"
والمخفي و الغير مألوف
and it's comprised of nearly 70 images.
وانها تضم ما يقرب من ٧٠ صورة.
In this context I'll just show you a few.
سأعرض القليل منها
This is a nuclear waste storage and encapsulation facility
هذا هو تخزين النفايات النووية ومرفق التغليف
at Hanford site in Washington State,
في موقع هانفورد في ولاية واشنطن ،
where there are over 1,900
حيث يوجد أكثر من ألف وتسعمائة
stainless steel capsules containing nuclear waste
من كبسولات الفولاذ المقاوم للصدأ المحتوية على النفايات النووية
submerged in water.
المغمورة بالمياه.
A human standing in front of an unprotected capsule would die instantly.
إذا وقف إنسان أمام كبسولة دون وقاية, قد يموت على الفور.
And I found one section amongst all of these
ولقد وجدت باب واحد من بين كل تلك
that actually resembled the outline
التي في الواقع تشبه مخطط
of the United States of America,
الولايات المتحدة الأمريكية.
which you can see here.
التي ترونها هنا.
And a big part of the work that is
وجزء كبير من العمل
sort of absent in this context is text.
الغائب نوع ما في هذا السياق هو النص.
So I create these two poles.
لذلك صنعت هذين القطبين.
Every image is accompanied with a very detailed factual text.
كل صورة يرافقها نص مفصل و واقعي.
And what I'm most interested in
و معظم ما أهمني
is the invisible space between a text
هو المساحة الغير مرئية بين النص
and its accompanying image,
و الصورة التي ترافقه،
and how the image is transformed by the text
و كيفية تحويل الصورة بواسطة النص،
and the text by the image.
والنص بواسطة الصورة.
So, at best, the image is meant to float away
لذلك ، في أحسن الأحوال ، الصورة مقصودة أن تطفو بعيدا
into abstraction and multiple truths and fantasy.
في التجريد وحقائق متعددة والخيال.
And then the text functions as this cruel anchor
ومن ثم النص يلعب دور المرساة القاسية
that kind of nails it to the ground.
التي هي نوع من المسامير في الأرض.
But in this context I'm just going to read
ولكن في هذا السياق سأقرأ فقط
an abridged version of those texts.
النسخة مختصرة من تلك النصوص.
This is a cryopreservation unit,
هذه هي وحدة تجميد .
and it holds the bodies of the wife and mother
وانها تحتوي على جثتي الزوجة والأم
of cryonics pioneer Robert Ettinger,
لرائد حفظ الموتى بالتجميد روبرت إيتنغر ،
who hoped to be awoken one day to extended life
الذي كان يأمل في أن استيقظ يوما واحدا لحياة ممتدة ،
in good health, with advancements in science and technology,
في صحة جيدة ، مع التقدم في العلوم والتكنولوجيا.
all for the cost of 35 thousand dollars, for forever.
كل هذا لتكلفة قدرها ٣٥ ألف دولار ، للأبد.
This is a 21-year-old Palestinian woman
هذه امرأة فلسطينية تبلغ من العمر ٢١ سنة
undergoing hymenoplasty.
تخضع لعملية غشاء البكارة
Hymenoplasty is a surgical procedure which restores the virginal state,
غشاء البكارة هي إجراء عملية جراحية التي تعيد الوضع العذري ،
allowing her to adhere to certain cultural expectations
مما يسمح لها لملاقاة بعض التوقعات الثقافية
regarding virginity and marriage.
حول العذرية والزواج.
So it essentially reconstructs a ruptured hymen,
إذاً فإنه يعيد أساسا غشاء البكارة المتمزق ،
allowing her to bleed upon having sexual intercourse,
مما يسمح لها أن تنزف عند الجماع الجنسي ،
to simulate the loss of virginity.
ليبرهن فقدان العذرية.
This is a jury simulation deliberation room,
هذه هي هيئة محلفين المحاكاة في غرفة المداولة ،
and you can see beyond that two-way mirror
ويمكنك رؤية خلف تلك المرآة باتجاهين
jury advisers standing in a room behind the mirror.
المستشارين المحلفين يقفون في غرفة وراء المرآة.
And they observe deliberations
وانهم يلاحظون المداولات
after mock trial proceedings
بعد إجراءات محاكمة صورية
so that they can better advise their clients how to adjust their trial strategy
حتى يتمكنوا من تقديم النصيحة لعملائهم بشكل أفضل بكيفية ضبط استراتيجية محاكمتهم
to have the outcome that they're hoping for.
ليصلوا للنتائج التي يأملونها.
This process costs 60,000 dollars.
هذه العملية تكلف ٦٠ ألف دولار.
This is a U.S. Customs and Border Protection room,
هذه غرفة الجمارك وحماية الحدود الأميركية،
a contraband room, at John F. Kennedy International Airport.
غرفة الممنوعات ، في مطار جون كنيدي الدولي.
On that table you can see 48 hours' worth
في هذا الجدول ترون حصيلة عمل ٤٨ ساعة
of seized goods from passengers entering in to the United States.
للسلع التي يصادروها من الركاب القادمين الى الولايات المتحدة.
There is a pig's head and African cane rats.
يوجد رأس خنزير وجرذان القصب الأفريقية .
And part of my photographic work
وجزء من عملي الفوتوغرافي
is I'm not just documenting what's there.
هو ليس فقط توثيق ما هناك.
I do take certain liberties and intervene.
أنا أمارس بعض الحرية وأتدخل .
And in this I really wanted it to resemble
وفي هذا أنا حقاً اردته أن يشابه
an early still-life painting,
لوحة في سن مبكر ما تزال حية.
so I spent some time with the smells and items.
لهذا قضيت بعض الوقت مع الروائح والبنود.
This is the exhibited art on the walls of the CIA
هذا هو الفن المعروض على جدران وكالة المخابرات المركزية
in Langley, Virginia, their original headquarters building.
في لانغلي ، فرجينيا ، مبنى المقر الأصلي.
And the CIA has had a long history
وكالة المخابرات المركزية الامريكية لديها تاريخ طويل
with both covert and public cultural diplomacy efforts.
مع كل الجهود سرية والعلنية الدبلوماسية الثقافية.
And it's speculated that some of their interest in the arts
وقد تكهن البعض بأن بعض إهتمامهم بالفنون
was designed to counter Soviet communism
كانت مصممة لمواجهة الشيوعية السوفياتية،
and promote what it considered to be pro-American
وترويج ما يعتبر مؤيدا للولايات المتحدة
thoughts and aesthetics.
كالأفكار والجماليات.
And one of the art forms that elicited the interest of the agency,
وواحدة من الأشكال الفنية التي أثارت اهتمام الوكالة ،
and had thus come under question, is abstract expressionism.
وبذلك تكون قد تعرضت لسؤال ، هو التعبير التجريدي.
This is the Forensic Anthropology Research Facility,
هذه منشأة لبحوث التشريح والأنثروبولوجيا.
and on a six acre plot
وعلى مساحة ستة أفدنة
there are approximately 75 cadavers at any given time
هناك ما يقرب ٧٥ جثة في أي وقت معين ،
that are being studied by forensic anthropologists
التي هي قيد الدراسة من قبل الأطباء الشرعيين
and researchers who are interested in monitoring
والباحثين المهتمين في مجال رصد
a rate of corpse decomposition.
معدل تحليل الجثة.
And in this particular photograph the body of a young boy
وفي هذه صورة بالذات, جثة صبي صغير
has been used to reenact a crime scene.
قد استخدم ليعيدون تمثيل مشهد الجريمة.
This is the only federally funded site
هذا هو الموقع الوحيد الممول اتحاديا
where it is legal to cultivate cannabis
حيث يتم زراعة القنب الهندي القانونياً
for scientific research in the United States.
للبحث العلمي في الولايات المتحدة.
It's a research crop marijuana grow room.
انها بحوث غرفة محاصيل نمو الماريجوانا.
And part of the work that I hope for
وجزء من العمل الذي آمل من أجله
is that there is a sort of disorienting entropy
هو أن هناك نوعا من إرتباك في الكون
where you can't find any discernible formula in how these things --
حيث لا يمكنك العثور على أي صيغة يمكن تمييزه في كيفية هذه الأشياء --
they sort of awkwardly jump from government to science
انها نوع من القفز من الحكومة ممدودةً للعلوم
to religion to security --
إلى الدين إلى الأمن --
and you can't completely understand
ولا يمكنك أن تفهم تماما
how information is being distributed.
كيف يتم توزيع المعلومات.
These are transatlantic submarine communication cables
هذه هي كابلات اتصالات عبر المحيط الأطلسي
that travel across the floor of the Atlantic Ocean,
التي تمر عبر قاع المحيط الأطلسي،
connecting North America to Europe.
تربط أمريكا الشمالية بأوروبا.
They carry over 60 million simultaneous voice conversations,
أنها تحمل أكثر من ٦٠ مليون محادثة صوتية في وقت واحد.
and in a lot of the government and technology sites
و في الكثير من المواقع الحكومية والتكنولوجيا
there was just this very apparent vulnerability.
كان هناك فقط هذا الضعف الواضح للغاية .
This one is almost humorous because it feels like I could
هذه تقريبا من روح الدعابة لانه يشعر وكأنني أستطيع
just snip all of that conversation in one easy cut.
مجرد قص كل تلك المحادثة بعملية قطع سهلة.
But stuff did feel like it could have been taken
لكن الاشياء أشعرتني بأنها كانت سوف تتخذ
30 or 40 years ago, like it was locked in the Cold War era
منذ ٣٠ أو ٤٠ سنة الماضية، كأنها قد علقت في حقبة الحرب الباردة
and hadn't necessarily progressed.
لم تكن قد تقدمت بالضرورة.
This is a Braille edition of Playboy magazine.
هذه هي طبعة لغة بريل من مجلة بلاي بوي.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
And this is ... a division of the Library of Congress
وهذا هو... قسم من مكتبة الكونغرس
produces a free national library service
وتنتج لخدمة المكتبة الوطنية مجاناً
for the blind and visually impaired,
للمكفوفين وضعاف البصر.
and the publications they choose to publish
والمنشورات التي اختاروها أن تنشر
are based on reader popularity.
وتستند شعبية القارئ.
And Playboy is always in the top few.
وبلاي بوي دائما من القلائل في القمة.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
But you'd be surprised, they don't do the photographs. It's just the text.
لكن سوف تدهشون ، هم لا يقرأوا الصور ..فقط مجرد النص.
This is an avian quarantine facility
هذا هو مرفق الطيور الحجر الصحي
where all imported birds coming into America
حيث كافة أنواع الطيور مستوردة إلى أمريكا
are required to undergo a 30-day quarantine,
تحتاج للخضوع للحجر الصحي لمدة ٣٠ يوما ،
where they are tested for diseases
حيث يتم اختبار عليها للأمراض
including Exotic Newcastle Disease
بما في ذلك الأمراض نيوكاسل الغريبة
and Avian Influenza.
وانفلونزا الطيور.
This film shows
هذا الفيلم يظهر
the testing of a new explosive fill on a warhead.
اختبار لعبوة متفجرة جديدة على رأس حربي.
And the Air Armament Center
ومركز التسلح الجوي
at Eglin Air Force Base in Florida
قاعدة ايجلين للقوات الجوية في ولاية فلوريدا ،
is responsible for the deployment and testing
هو المسؤول عن نشر واختبار
of all air-delivered weaponry
جميع الأسلحة المسقطة من الجو
coming from the United States.
القادمة من الولايات المتحدة.
And the film was shot on 72 millimeter, government-issue film.
الفيلم كان مصوراً عن بعد ٧٢ ميليمتر، فيلم خاص بالحكومة
And that red dot is a marking on the government-issue film.
و تلك النقطة الحمراء التي تعلم على لمسألة فيلم الحكومة.
All living white tigers in North America
جميع النمور البيضاء التي تعيش في أمريكا الشمالية
are the result of selective inbreeding --
هي نتيجة لزواج الأقارب انتقائياً --
that would be mother to son,
التي من الممكن أن تكون الأم لابنها ،
father to daughter, sister to brother --
أب لابنته أو أخته لأخيه --
to allow for the genetic conditions
للسماح للشروط الجينية
that create a salable white tiger.
لتوليد النمر البيض الرائج.
Meaning white fur, ice blue eyes, a pink nose.
ما يعنى الفرو الأبيض والعيون الزرقاء، والأنف الوردي.
And the majority of these white tigers
وغالبية هذه النمور البيضاء
are not born in a salable state
لا يولدون في حالة رائجة ،
and are killed at birth.
ويتم قتلها عند الولادة.
It's a very violent process that is little known.
انها عملية عنيفة جدا والتي هي غير معروفة إلا القليل.
And the white tiger is obviously celebrated in several forms of entertainment.
ومن الواضح أن النمرالأبيض يحتفل به في العديد من أشكال الترفيه.
Kenny was born. He actually made it to adulthood.
ولد النمر كيني. و إستطاع الوصول إلى مرحلة البلوغ.
He has since passed away,
منذ ذلك ألحين‏ توفي،
but was mentally retarded
ولكن كان متخلف عقليا
and suffers from severe bone abnormalities.
ويعاني من تشوهات عظمية الشديدة.
This, on a lighter note, is at
هذا ، على مذكرة أخف وزنا ، هو في
George Lucas' personal archive.
جورج لوكاس 'المحفوظات الشخصية.
This is the Death Star.
هذه هي نجمة الموت.
And it's shown here in its true orientation.
وانها موضحه هنا في اتجاهها الصحيح.
In the context of "Star Wars: Return of the Jedi,"
في سياق حرب النجوم عودة الجيداي ،
its mirror image is presented.
قدمت صورتهاالطبق الأصل
They flip the negative.
انهم يقلبون النجاتيف
And you can see the photoetched brass detailing,
ويمكنك أن ترى رسومات الصورة النحاسية بالتفصيل ،
and the painted acrylic facade.
ورسمات واجهات الاكريليك.
In the context of the film,
في سياق الفيلم ،
this is a deep-space battle station of the Galactic Empire,
هذا هو الفضاء السحيق لمعركة محطة إمبراطورية المجرة ،
capable of annihilating planets and civilizations,
القادرة على إفناء الكواكب والحضارات.
and in reality it measures about four feet by two feet.
و في الحقيقة فهي بحجم أربعة أقدام في قدمين.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
This is at Fort Campbell in Kentucky.
هذه في قاعدة فورت كامبل في كنتاكي.
It's a Military Operations on Urbanized Terrain site.
انها عملية عسكرية في المناطق الحضرية.
Essentially they've simulated a city
أساسا انهم يحاكون المدينة
for urban combat,
للقتال في المناطق الحضارية.
and this is one of the structures that exists in that city.
وهذا هو واحد من الهياكل الموجودة في تلك المدينة.
It's called the World Church of God.
و انها تسمى كنيسة الله العالمية
It's supposed to be a generic site of worship.
فمن المفترض أن تكون مكاناً عاماً للعبادة.
And after I took this photograph,
وبعد أن أخذت هذه الصورة
they constructed a wall around the World Church of God
قاموا ببناء جدار حول كنيسة الله العالمية
to mimic the set-up of mosques in Afghanistan or Iraq.
لتقليد انشاء المساجد في أفغانستان أو العراق.
And I worked with Mehta Vihar
وعملت مع ميهتا فيهار
who creates virtual simulations for the army
الذي يصنع محاكاة افتراضية للجيش
for tactical practice.
للتجربة التكتيكية.
And we put that wall around the World Church of God,
ونضع هذا الجدار حول الكنيسة الله العالمية ،
and also used the characters and vehicles and explosions
واستخدم أيضا الشخصيات والمركبات والانفجارات
that are offered in the video games for the army.
التي يتم تقديمها لألعاب الفيديو التابعة للجيش.
And I put them into my photograph.
وأقوم بوضعهم في صوري.
This is live HIV virus
هذا هو فيروس نقص المناعة (إيدز) حي
at Harvard Medical School, who is working with the U.S. Government
في كلية الطب بجامعة هارفارد ، التي تعمل مع حكومة الولايات المتحدة
to develop sterilizing immunity.
لتطوير مناعة معقمة .
And Alhurra is a U.S. Government- sponsored
والحرة هي شبكة التلفزيون باللغة العربية
Arabic language television network
برعاية الحكومة الامريكية
that distributes news and information to over 22 countries in the Arab world.
التي توزع الأنباء والمعلومات لأكثر من ٢٢ بلدا في العالم العربي.
It runs 24 hours a day, commercial free.
انها تعمل ٢٤ ساعة يومياً، إعلانات مجانية
However, it's illegal to broadcast Alhurra within the United States.
ومع ذلك ، فإنه ممنوع بث الحرة داخل الولايات المتحدة.
And in 2004, they developed a channel called Alhurra Iraq,
وفي عام ٢٠٠٤ اطلقت قناة الحرة عراق ،
which specifically deals with events occurring in Iraq
وهي على وجه التحديد تتعامل مع الأحداث التي تقع في العراق
and is broadcast to Iraq.
وتبث الى العراق.
Now I'm going to move on to another project I did.
الآن سانتقال إلى مشروع آخر فعلته.
It's titled "The Innocents."
انه بعنوان الأبرياء.
And for the men in these photographs,
وبالنسبة للرجال في هذه الصور ،
photography had been used to create a fantasy.
التصوير استخدم لخلق الخيال.
Contradicting its function as evidence of a truth,
يتعارض مع وظيفتها باعتبارها دليلا على الحقيقة ،
in these instances it furthered the fabrication of a lie.
في هذه الحالات فانها عززت تلفيق الكذب.
I traveled across the United States
سافرت في جميع أنحاء الولايات المتحدة
photographing men and women who had been wrongfully convicted
تصوير الرجال والنساء الذين كانوا قد ادينوا ظلما
of crimes they did not commit, violent crimes.
بجرائم لم يرتكبوها ، جرائم عنف.
I investigate photography's ability to blur truth and fiction,
اني احقق في قدرات التصوير الفوتوغرافي لطمس الحقيقة والخيال،
and its influence on memory,
وتأثيرها على الذاكرة ،
which can lead to severe, even lethal consequences.
التي يمكن أن تؤدي إلى خواطر، أو حتى عواقب مميتة.
For the men in these photographs,
للرجال في هذه الصور
the primary cause of their wrongful conviction
السبب الرئيسي لادانتهم الغير المشروعة
was mistaken identification.
كانت مطابقه خاطئة.
A victim or eyewitness identifies
ضحيه أو شاهد عيان يحدد
a suspected perpetrator
جاني مشتبه به
through law enforcement's use of images.
من خلال إنفاذ القانون باستخدام الصور.
But through exposure to composite sketches,
ولكن من خلال التعرض لتركيب الرسومات ،
Polaroids, mug shots and line-ups,
مادة مستقطبه للضوء‏ ، صورة الوجه والاصطفاف ،
eyewitness testimony can change.
شهادات شهود العيان يمكن ان تتغير.
I'll give you an example from a case.
سأعطيكم مثالا من هذه الحالة.
A woman was raped and presented with a series of photographs
امرأة تعرضت للاغتصاب ، وقدمت لها سلسلة من الصور الفوتوغرافية
from which to identify her attacker.
لتحديد المعتدي عليها.
She saw some similarities in one of the photographs,
شاهدت بعض أوجه التشابه في واحدة من الصور ،
but couldn't quite make a positive identification.
لكن لم تمكن تماما أن تحدد مطابقة إيجابية .
Days later, she is presented with another photo array
بعد بضعة أيام قُدم لها مجموعة أخرى من الصور
of all new photographs,
جميعها صور جديدة.
except that one photograph that she had some draw to
ما عدا الصورة التي رسمتها من قبل
from the earlier array is repeated in the second array.
من السلسلة السابقة ، تكررت في المجموعة الثانية.
And a positive identification is made
وتم التعرف على شخصية
because the photograph replaced the memory,
لأن الصورة حلّت محل الذاكرة ،
if there ever was an actual memory.
إذا كان هناك في الأصل ذاكرة حقيقية.
Photography offered the criminal justice system
التصوير يقدم لنظام العدالة ضد المجرمين
a tool that transformed innocent citizens into criminals,
أداة تقوم بتحويل المواطنين الأبرياء إلى مجرمين.
and the criminal justice system failed to recognize the limitations
ونظام العدالة على المجرمين فشل في تحقيق فواصل
of relying on photographic identifications.
للاعتماد على التعرف الفوتوغرافية.
Frederick Daye, who is photographed at his alibi location,
فردريك داي ، الذي تم تصويره في موقع المدعي عليه ،
where 13 witnesses placed him at the time of the crime.
حيث أكد ١٣ شاهدا عليه في وقت ارتكاب الجريمة.
He was convicted by an all-white jury
أدين من قبل هيئة محلفين
of rape, kidnapping and vehicle theft.
بالاغتصاب والخطف وسرقة السيارات.
And he served 10 years of a life sentence.
وخدم ١٠ اعوام بعقوبة السجن مدى الحياة.
Now DNA exonerated Frederick
الآن برأ الحمض النووي فردريك
and it also implicated another man
كما أنه ورط رجل آخر
who was serving time in prison.
الذي كان يقضي فترة في السجن.
But the victim refused to press charges
ولكن الضحية رفض توجيه اتهامات
because she claimed that law enforcement
لأنها ادعت أن إنفاذ القانون
had permanently altered her memory through the use of Frederick's photograph.
قد يغير بشكل دائم ذاكرتها من خلال استخدام صورة لفردريك.
Charles Fain was convicted of kidnapping, rape and murder
تشارلز فاين أدين بالاختطاف والاغتصاب والقتل
of a young girl walking to school.
فتاة صغيرة في طريقها الى مدرستها.
He served 18 years of a death sentence.
خدم ١٨ عاما من عقوبة الاعدام.
I photographed him at the scene of the crime
قمت بتصويره في مكان الجريمة
at the Snake River in Idaho.
في نهر سنيك في ولاية ايداهو.
And I photographed all of the wrongfully convicted
وصورت كل من أدين ظلما
at sites that came to particular significance
في المواقع التي جاءت لأهمية خاصة
in the history of their wrongful conviction.
في تاريخ إدانتهم الخاطئة.
The scene of arrest, the scene of misidentification,
مكان الاعتقال ، ومكان التعرف الخطأ عليهم ،
the alibi location.
موقع المدعي عليهم.
And here, the scene of the crime, it's this place
وهنا ، في مشهد الجريمة ، إنه المكان
to which he's never been, but changed his life forever.
الذي لم يزوره في حياته، ولكن غير حياته الى الابد.
So photographing there, I was hoping to highlight
لذا فالتصوير هناك ، كنت آمل أن أسلط الضوء على
the tenuous relationship between truth and fiction,
العلاقة الواهية بين الحقيقة والخيال ،
in both his life and in photography.
في كلا حياته والصور.
Calvin Washington was convicted of capital murder.
كالفن واشنطن اتهم بالقتل .
He served 13 years of a life sentence in Waco, Texas.
خدم ١٣ عاما بعقوبة السجن مدى الحياة في واكو بولاية تكساس.
Larry Mayes, I photographed at the scene of arrest,
لاري ميس ، صورته في مكان القبض عليه ،
where he hid between two mattresses in Gary, Indiana,
حيث اختبأ بين فرشتين في غاري، ولاية انديانا ،
in this very room to hide from the police.
في هذه القاعة بالذات للاختباء من الشرطة.
He ended up serving 18 and a half years
انتهى به المطاف بخدمة ١٨ سنة ونصف السنة
of an 80 year sentence for rape and robbery.
من جملة حكم قضائي لمدة ٨٠ سنة بعقوبه الاغتصاب والسرقة
The victim failed to identify Larry
فشلت الضحية في التعرف على لاري
in two live lineups
في إصطفافين مباشرين
and then made a positive identification, days later,
ومن ثم حددت مطابقة إيجابية ، بعد بضعة أيام ،
from a photo array.
من مجموعة صور فوتوغرافية.
Larry Youngblood served eight years of a 10 and half year sentence
لاري يونغبلود خدم ثمانية أعوام من عقوبة ١٠ سنوات ونصف
in Arizona for the abduction and repeated sodomizing
في ولاية اريزونا بتهمة الاختطاف وتكرار ممارسة اللواط
of a 10 year old boy at a carnival.
مع صبي يبلغ من العمر ١٠ سنوات في مهرجان .
He is photographed at his alibi location.
إنه مصور في مكان الإدعاء.
Ron Williamson. Ron was convicted of the rape and murder
رون ويليامسون ، أدين رون بتهمة اغتصاب وقتل
of a barmaid at a club,
لنادلة في نادي ،
and served 11 years of a death sentence.
وخدم ١١ عاما من عقوبة الاعدام.
I photographed Ron at a baseball field
صورت رون في حقل البيسبول
because he had been drafted to the Oakland A's
لكونه كان مدعو إلى فريق واوكلاند آيس
to play professional baseball just before his conviction.
للعب البيسبول باحتراف قبل إدانته بالضبط .
And the state's key witness in Ron's case
الشاهد الرئيسي في قضية رون
was, in the end, the actual perpetrator.
كان ، في نهاية المطاف ، مرتكب الجريمة الفعلي.
Ronald Jones served eight years of a death sentence
رونالد جونز خدم ثمانية أعوام من حكم الاعدام
for rape and murder of a 28-year-old woman.
بتهمة اغتصاب وقتل امرأة بعمر ٢٨ سنة.
I photographed him at the scene of arrest in Chicago.
صورته في مكان اعتقاله في شيكاغو.
William Gregory was convicted of rape and burglary.
ويليام غريغوري ادين بالاغتصاب والسرقة.
He served seven years of a 70 year sentence in Kentucky.
خدم سبع سنوات من الحكم لمدة ٧٠ سنة في ولاية كنتاكي.
Timothy Durham, who I photographed at his alibi location
تيموثي دورهام ، الذي صورته في موقع الإدعاء
where 11 witnesses placed him at the time of the crime,
حيث شهد عليه ١١ شاهدا في وقت وقوع الجريمة ،
was convicted of 3.5 years
وقضى عقوبة ثلاث سنوات ونصف
of a 3220 year sentence,
من عقوبة ال ٣٢٢٠ سنة
for several charges of rape and robbery.
بعدة إتهامات من الاغتصاب والسرقة.
He had been misidentified by an 11-year-old victim.
كان قد أخطئ في التعرف عليه من قبل الضحية البالغ من العمر ١١ سنة
Troy Webb is photographed here at the scene of the crime in Virginia.
تروي ويب تم تصويره هنا في مسرح الجريمة في ولاية فرجينيا.
He was convicted of rape, kidnapping and robbery,
أدين بتهمة الاغتصاب والاختطاف والسرقة ،
and served seven years of a 47 year sentence.
وخدم سبع سنوات من حكم ال-٤٧ سنة.
Troy's picture was in a photo array
صورة "تروي" كانت في مجموعة الصور
that the victim tentatively had some draw toward,
التي رسمها الضحية
but said he looked too old.
لكنه قال انه يبدو كبير جدا.
The police went and found a photograph of Troy Webb
توجهت الشرطة و وجدت صورة تروي ويب
from four years earlier,
قبل أربع سنوات من ذلك الوقت
which they entered into a photo array days later,
التي دخلت في مجموعة الصور بعد بضعة أيام،
and he was positively identified.
و تم التعرف عليه.
Now I'm going to leave you with a self portrait.
والأن سأترككم مع هذه الصورة.
And it reiterates that distortion is a constant,
انها تكرر أن هذا التشويه هو ثابت ،
and our eyes are easily deceived.
و أن عيوننا سهلة الخداع
That's it. Thank you.
هذا كل شيء. شكرا لكم.
(Applause)
(تصفيق)